{"id":"2018_28","name":"","memoryVerse":"\"Lord, the God of Israel, there is no God like you in heaven above or on earth below--you who keep your covenant of love with your servants who continue wholeheartedly in your way.\" â€“ 1 Kings 8:23","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.\nUse this space to record how you have seen God's activity during the week. (How has He provided, answered, comforted, reconciled, guided, etc.?)\nFrom the past week's study, what made the most significant impact to you in the notes, lecture, group sharing or personal study?","questions":[]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read 1 Kings 9:1-9.\nThe Lord appeared to Solomon a second time.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"9:1-9"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_28_3","questionText":"3. What had Solomon accomplished at the point the Lord appeared to him a second time? (1 Kings 4:24-34)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"4:24-34"}]},{"id":"2018_28_4","questionText":"4. What warnings and promises did God make to Solomon? What was the point of these words?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_5","questionText":"5. What does it look like to \"walk faithfully with integrity of heart and uprightness\"? How is this reminder relevant in your current circumstances?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read 1 Kings 9:10-28; 2 Chronicles 8.\nSolomon built his kingdom.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"9:10-28"},{"book":"2 Chronicles","verse":"8:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_28_6","questionText":"6. What was the focus of Solomon's time and energy during these years?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_7","questionText":"7. How did Solomon demonstrate both wisdom and questionable judgment?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_8","questionText":"8. What does the way you spend your time and energy say about you? How do you measure the success of a pursuit?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read 1 Kings 10:1-13.\nThe Queen of Sheba visited Solomon.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"10:1-13"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_28_9","questionText":"9. What drew the Queen of Sheba to Solomon? Once she met him, what impressed the Queen of Sheba about Solomon?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_10","questionText":"10. What conclusion did the Queen of Sheba make about having a ruler who applies godly wisdom? What conclusion did she make about God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_11","questionText":"11. Compare the similarities and differences between King Solomon and King Jesus. Perhaps you are wondering if Jesus is all that He claims to be. What hard questions would you like to ask Jesus? (Use any reference in Scripture.)","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read 1 Kings 10:14-29; Psalm 72.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"10:14-29"},{"book":"Psalm","verse":"72:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_28_12","questionText":"12. Psalm 72 is a prayer of David for his son Solomon. How was this prayer answered through Solomon's life? For whom does this encourage you to pray?","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"72:1-999"}]},{"id":"2018_28_13","questionText":"13. What does Solomon's experience reveal about the blessings and challenges of great wealth and talent? What is the lesson for you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review 1 Kings 9-10; Psalm 72","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"9:1-10:999"},{"book":"Psalm","verse":"72:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_28_14","questionText":"14. What is the most important or challenging thing you learned this week?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_28_15","questionText":"15. Homiletics for group and administrative leaders: 1 Kings 9-10.","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Kings","verse":"9:1-10:999"}]}]}}}